# ANTHONY DO

Taylorsville, UT • (801) 652-7975 <a href="mailto:anthonydo888@gmail.com">anthonydo888@gmail.com</a> • linkedin.com/in/dosanity

### **SUMMARY**

Multi-talented, ambitious individual with a diverse knowledge and skill set. Strong quantitative problem-solving expertise with creative intellect. Comfortable in learning and achieving new ideas and extremely adaptable in different environments. Highly proficient in statistical analysis through programming but also in graphic design.

#### **EDUCATION**

**University of Utah** 

Salt Lake City, UT

Honors Bachelor of Science - Double Major

May 2022

Applied Mathematics and QAMO (Quantitative Analysis of Markets and Organizations),

Analytics, Finance, & Statistical Analysis Emphasis, Economics minor

#### Honors

- Diversity of Merit received due to high academic performance.
- Honors College program for honor students that show remarkable achievements.
- Opportunity Scholars program for high achieving students to explore business through different opportunities.
- Dean's List, 3.9 GPA overall, 3.96 in Mathematics.

#### **Related Coursework**

- Honors Financial Management financial analysis, planning, and decision making to maximize the value of firms.
- Data Science data wrangling and analysis using Python to statistically predict outcomes.
- Game Theory maximizing behaviors by quantifying through calculus and probability.

#### **SKILLS**

- Licenses: Series 7, Series 63, & SIE
- Software: Microsoft Office & Adobe Creative Cloud (Illustrator, Lightroom, & Photoshop)
- Languages: English & Cantonese
- Programming: Python, R, STATA, HTML, & CSS

## **EXPERIENCE**

#### **Fidelity Investments**

Salt Lake City, UT

Customer Relationship Advocate

June 2021 – Present

• Financial representative licensed in the Series 7, Series 63, and SIE to support clients with equity trading and allocation of funds.

#### **Taylorsville Recreation Center**

Salt Lake City, UT

Front Desk

August 2017 – May 2022

- Provide customer support to effectively direct customers to different facilities available.
- Register and organize different activities through sales.

## **Business Leaders Incorporated**

Salt Lake City, UT

Chief Marketing Officer

*April* 2019 – May 2021

- Oversaw the marketing committee and coordinates communication between 4 boards.
- Designed creative advertisement techniques through Adobe Illustrator, Photoshop, & Lightroom.

#### A. Ray Olpin University Union

Salt Lake City, UT

Associate Director of Marketing

*April* 2018 – *June* 2019

• Initiated a powerful advertisement campaign for the Crimson Board that reached 15% of 30,000 students with the use of Adobe applications and designs.

### **ACTIVITIES**

### **Utah System of Higher Education**, STEP-UP Ambassador

*May 2018 – June 2019* 

• Selected to support students to enter higher education through volunteering at local high schools and administering different promotions.

## Business Scholars, Member

*September 2017 – May 2022* 

• Chosen as 1 of 350 students to participate in honors program for students at the David Eccles School of Business to explore and understand all areas of business through coursework, projects, and company interactions.